Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
(wind howling)
(heart monitor beeps steadily)
(whispers) I'm so cold.
Why is there no heat?
(exhales)
(heart monitor echoes)
(whispers) Riley.
(whispers) Magnus.
Come with me.
You stupid girl.
I told you this would happen.
(voice breaks) I'm sorry.
You've been apologizing
your whole life.
You won't have to anymore.
- (gasps softly)
- (Yrsa) Yes...
you're going to die here.
- (gasps)
- What? God, what? Nomi! Wh-- What is it?
They know what she is.
They're gonna cut her open.
They're gonna turn her into a Bolger.
We gotta do something.
Bu-- What?
We need information.
We need to know if BPO has been alerted,
if someone's made the diagnosis...
I could hack into the hospital
in a second,
but I don't have any equipment.
They took everything.
Can't you... use your police codes
or something and call them?
- Is that the cop?
- Yeah.
I was suspended.
- Great.
- What?
- He got suspended.
- Great.
(Nomi) What do we do?
(knocking at door)
I-- I wouldn't answer that.
No one looking for a fugitive
would knock like that.
(Neets breathes heavily, gasps)
Bug!
Hello, Angels.
Bug, what are you doing here?
Feds are funny, you know.
They spend all that money
protecting things that nobody cares about.
Then they leave
the real information lying around
like a Post-it note on a refrigerator.
For instance, when they confiscate
illegal electronic equipment,
it's inventoried to a site...
that's like a shopping list
to a guy like me.
So-- Thank you, baby.
So when I saw exactly the things
that I had just sold you posted,
well... the Bug suspected foul play.
Oh, I-- I don't have
any money to pay you, Bug.
I didn't come for money.
I'd still be in prison
if it weren't for you, Mike.
I mean Nomi. Nomi.
Look, I don't know what kind of fight
you're getting yourself into, but...
I do know... you can't shoot back
without any bullets in your gun.
So...
consider yourselves... reloaded.
Oh...
Hey, partner. What's up?
I thought we agreed
we'd be starting tomorrow.
(sighs) We did, but, uh...
there's something I have to do,
and I need a favor.
Who's this?
Hey, beautiful girl. I'm Jela.
What's your name?
I'm Amondi Kabaka.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Jela.
I was hoping she could stay here with you.
I believe someone else
will come by later to collect her.
Where will you be?
If it gets too late...
here is the number of her French teacher.
She will know what to do.
Capheus... where are you going?
I have to settle a debt.
- You're coming back, aren't you?
- (Capheus chuckles)
Van Damme always comes back.
Take care of her, Jela.
I will.
(Jela) Hey, Van Damme.
See you tomorrow.
(Rajan) The doctors are saying
it's a miracle he's still alive.
I'm not sure which
would upset my father more:
the idea of fanatics trying to kill him,
or a god getting credit for saving him.
How is your mother?
As he improves, she becomes convinced...
that it's because she's praying again.
She wants to go to the temple with you.
Rajan? I know you
want to get back to the hospital...
It's actually nice to get outside,
so thank you.
Though I am a little nervous about
what you've been wanting to talk about.
It's about... something I didn't
tell the police when they questioned me
about the attack on your father.
It had no bearing on what happened.
It was... a private matter.
As such,
I felt that I should tell only you.
Your father did not want us
to get married.
He told me that he had reconsidered
and asked me to say no to you,
for your own good.
He thought that we were not well matched.
What did you say?
There was no time
to say very much of anything.
How difficult it must have been
for you to hold all this inside.
I thought it was important
for you to know.
A lesser woman would have said
he wished us well,
that he wanted us
to be married no matter what...
and he gave us his blessings.
And I would have known that she was lying.
You knew he was against our marriage?
Of course.
So is that what I was to you?
- An act of rebellion against your father?
- Never.
I told you the truth.
Maybe it added a bit of spice
to my attraction to you,
but it has nothing to do
with why I asked you to marry me.
I want you to marry me,
not to be for or against anyone else,
because I love you,
I trust you...
and I can imagine no better life
than growing old with you.
All I need to know now is...
after everything that has happened,
do you still want to marry me?
(typing)
(Nomi) OK, I fixed it so that
any information, requisition or test
that goes out with her name on it
will look like spam to other computers.
Great. So she's safe.
I figure they would've moved her
somewhere more secure if they knew,
like they did to me.
- (sighs) Her poor father.
- Yeah.
He's been there the whole time.
(singing "Baba O'Riley")
How is she?
She's still in the ICU...
but she's not alone.
(indistinct chatter)
(man whistles)
(men cheering)
- (speaks Swahili)
- (excited chatter)
(shouts in Swahili)
(speaking Swahili)
You are a smart man, Van Damme!
(singsong) Come on out.
Eh?
(chattering in Swahili)
It's empty!
Where is she?
Amondi. Where the fuck is the girl?!
She has nothing to do with this.
(screams) Bullshit!
She's Kabaka's daughter.
(Capheus) She's just a child.
He killed my sister.
I'm here because
you have a quarrel with me,
not my mother... and not a child.
Let us settle our debt...
like men.
(metal scraping)
Like men?
Like men?!
(laughter)
Like men!
You are hilarious.
I like you, Van Damme.
Come!
- Walk!
- (chatter in Swahili)
(men cheering)
You have a visitor.
Sun...
(guard) No touching!
Sister...
it's good to see you.
What are you doing here, Joong-Ki?
(sighs) There's no easy way to say this.
Last night, Father was very upset.
He was drinking.
You know how he can be.
I told him to go home.
He said he couldn't.
He said he was a failure, that he deserved
no home, that he deserved to die.
I couldn't listen to him anymore.
I left.
I wish to God I hadn't, but I did.
I have to live with that mistake.
We had a meeting this morning.
He never showed up.
I had everyone looking for him.
I had a lunch...
when the police showed up.
They found him.
He was in his car.
A hose connected
the exhaust to the window.
But the police are wrong.
He didn't kill himself.
It was shame.
Like a kind of cancer.
Shame killed our father.
Sun... we cannot blame ourselves, OK?
What happened was beyond our control.
But I didn't want you
to hear it from someone else.
That's why I had to come myself.
(breath quivering)
I'm so sorry.
At least... we still have each other.
You killed him.
You... killed him.
(sniffles)
Sun... I know this is a terrible blow.
He was going
to tell the truth to the court,
so you had to stop him,
because you're afraid of prison.
(sniffs)
Sun...
do not say something
you're going to regret.
The police said it was a suicide.
You murdered... our father.
(whispers) I was nowhere near him.
(sniffs) OK...
obviously, you're upset.
(Sun screams)
(Joong-Ki grunts)
(Joong-Ki) Help!
- (guard) Hey! Hey!
- (Joong-Ki) Help!
(Joong-Ki screams)
(Sun shouts, grunts)
Look at me.
Look at me, Joong-Ki!
I know what you did.
You will pay.
I swear it!
- (men cheering)
- (man shouts in Swahili)
- (in English) Superpower!
- (cheering)
(men chatter in Swahili)
(cheering)
Bring out the bitch!
We've been trying
to house-train her, but...
once a street bitch,
always a street bitch.
- (grunts)
- (coughing)
Keeps pissing herself.
(whimpers softly)
See... I was going
to make this bitch watch me
as I killed the only thing
in her life that mattered.
But... I have a better idea.
(snaps fingers)
(Silas whimpering)
I want you to do the honor
and put this bitch out of her misery.
You do it.
You cut her fucking head off...
and we'll call our debt even.
It's a little dull.
You might have to hack a few times...
but you can do it.
You are Van-fucking-Damme.
(chuckles)
(whispers) Do it quick!
Come on, Van Damme.
Like a man, huh?
Like a man!
(Silas sobbing)
What's the problem?
I'll tell you the problem.
The problem is... you aren't a man.
You're just another bitch!
(Silas whimpering)
Bitch, come on!
(grunting)
It's you or him, bitch!
(softly) Call me a bitch one more time...
and I will kill you.
Say what?
Bitch!
- (screams)
- (Sun shouts)
(man screams)
- (Sun) Aah!
- (man shouts)
(grunting) Aah!
(chuckles)
(Sun shouts)
(screams)
Van Damme.
Fucking Van Damme.
(sighs)
(engine revving)
What the fuck are you doing here?
(groans)
(screams) Find them!
(Wolfgang) "What's best in life?
Crush your enemies,
see them driven before you,
and hear the lamentations
of their women."
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- No... it's we who should thank you.
- This means so much.
- Yes, so much.
Remover of obstacles.
As the obstacle to our faith was removed.
- What are you... talking--
- She is our hero.
She brought him here.
- No.
- Yes. God worked through you.
- No!
- Yes. You brought the defiler to us.
You brought him
where we could reach him at last.
No one likes violence.
God does not like violence.
This is obscene!
But he knows...
sometimes it is necessary--
No, don't touch me.
You have nothing to be afraid of.
- You are one of us.
- (man) Yes.
- (woman) Yes.
- No!
(man) You're one of us!
Don't touch her!
If I see you... any of you, here again,
I will show you what violence looks like.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Come on, come on!
Let's go.
Thank you.
They'll be back.
- So will I.
- Well...
so will I.
This is India. Wow.
Uh, where are you?
Chicago... sort of.
Sort of?
My thoughts aren't really there.
They're with her.
(softly) I remember listening to music.
Yeah, her father
was playing with the orchestra,
and it triggered something in her.
- What is wrong with her?
- I'm not sure.
I'm afraid that soon
they'll realize what she is.
And then?
I don't know.
- Are we clear?
- I don't know.
Van Damme-- Capheus, thank you.
Thank you for not giving them Amondi.
I'm going to make you a rich man.
I don't want your money, sir.
You can keep it.
Tell me then, why did you save me?
To be honest,
it wasn't exactly a part of my plan.
Oh, no!
Any weapons in here? Knives, guns?
No, no, I don't have any weapons.
- Capheus!
- (Will) What is it? What's the matter?
I think I'm about to die.
Nobody's gonna die.
(grunts)
Buckle up!
- (screams)
- (man shouting)
Move, move, move, move. Move!
- Fuck!
- (man shouts in Swahili)
(horns honking)
Move, move, move!
Sorry!
(engine revving)
(whispers) Shit!
(tires squealing)
(motorcycle approaching)
Oh, shit!
- (gun clicking)
- Shit!
(engine revving)
Is he gone?
Let's settle this.
(revving)
(screams)
(gunshot)
(screaming)
Aah!
You will take good care of him,
you understand?
If anyone comes looking
for a man matching his description,
you say nothing, you do nothing,
you call me.
How long will it be?
What I have to do now...
shouldn't take long.
What name should I use?
Conan.
Is that a first name, a last name?
Yes.
(indistinct chatter)
Try it.
Nice.
Capheus!
Capheus...
Ah! Capheus!
Oh, my God!
I knew you'd come back.
Van Damme always comes back.
Papa, are you all right?
I'm fine.
No, I'm better than fine.
I'm lucky.
- Who loves you?
- You do.
- (heart monitor beeps steadily)
- (exhales)
(wind howling)
(sharp inhale)
(woman) I've never seen anything like it.
The growth of the substantia alba.
(exhales) I'm so cold.
(Magnus) Here, take my coat.
No.
- No!
- (monitor beeps rapidly)
I can't believe she can even move
with what we've given her.
Kids today have
huge tolerance for drugs.
(heart monitor stabilizes)
- Did we hear back from the neurologist?
- Not yet. Still waiting.
Did you do that?
It was easy.
Hacking's what I do.
Did you do this, too?
How'd you get access
to the Australian fugitive alert?
I'm an all-access kind of girl.
Looks totally real, doesn't it?
I figured it would
buy us a little more time.
That's the question.
How much time do we have,
how much time does she have?
None. You're out of time.
Jonas.
I told you I made a mistake.
I wish there was some way to fix it,
but there's not.
I was just afraid if I didn't help you,
you wouldn't be alive right now.
That's not a mistake, that's true.
No, the mistake was mine.
I should've trusted you.
The real question we face is,
can you trust me now?
Yes.
Even when I tell you
that Whispers knows about Riley?
How? I have all the information
locked down.
You know about her
and Will knows about her...
and I know you.
And Whispers... knows me.
Be careful what you tell them.
Not too much, or they won't believe you.
He's here with me now.
He wants me to tell you
that he's going to Iceland,
that he's going to find Riley,
and once he does, it won't be long
until he finds the rest of you.
And why would he tell us that?
Why not just go straight to Iceland
or have Riley arrested?
Tell Will I look forward to meeting him.
Don't underestimate him, Will.
He's very good at manipulating people.
Right now he's smiling because
he knows the only thought in your head
is getting on the next plane to Iceland.
This is a bad place.
You should not be here.
You don't have to do this.
You could just... turn around.
It is so simple a thing, just...
just turn the wheel,
and the future changes.
- It is not that simple.
- It is.
You stopped your wedding,
but it's still going to happen.
You don't know that.
Some things in our lives are inevitable.
Don't do this.
They will kill you.
There are worse things than dying.
Wolfgang, please!
There are things I will never be able
to understand about your world,
just as there are things
you will never understand about mine.
I understand how I feel about you.
And somehow, I know
that you feel the same way about me.
This is why I'm here.
After what I did...
as long as that man is alive...
no one I care about will ever be safe.
(console beeps)
It's Wolfgang.
(Sun) Crying won't help him.
I can feel what you're feeling.
This is what life is.
Fear, rage, desire... love.
To stop feeling emotions,
to stop wanting to feel them...
is to feel... death.
What do you suggest I do?
I take everything I am feeling...
everything that matters to me...
I push all of it... into my fist...
and I fight for it.
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net