Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
This isn't a fair fight.
We need to level the playing field
and that's what this guy does.
And you trust him?
Because you were hackers together?
Because he got caught
hacking the Pentagon during the war.
Couldn't have been very serious.
- It was.
- Then why isn't he in jail?
Because I took the fall for him.
I was a juvenile. I had rich parents.
I got off with community service.
I never told you because I didn't think
that I would ever have to revisit
this part of my life.
I'm sorry.
Attention.
This is Prisoner 773.
Teach her the rules.
It is her.
Here he comes.
- The embezzler.
- You stole all of those investors' money?
Shamed your father and brother.
And almost destroyed their company.
Well done.
Hey, Bug.
Where's Mike?
It's me. I'm... Mike.
Oh, shit.
Fuck!
Right, totally forgot.
I'm a fucking idiot.
'Course it's you, buddy!
'Course it's you.
Not you, like the old you,
like a new, hot version of you.
Shit, Mike.
You're a total fox!
I would do you! I would.
I would totally... I mean not like,
not in a degrading way, like that sounded,
but total compliment.
- Thank you.
- Her name's Nomi.
OK.
- Who's this?
- This is my girlfriend.
- Seriously? Shit!
- Bug.
Right.
Business.
Everything you need.
Right here.
Hey, look, if you guys are startin'
some crime-fightin' super-team
Charlie's Angels shit,
you count me in.
OK. Let's start you off
with some switch hooks.
I need a candygram and a feedtrough
that'll burrow through
any firewall ever built.
Things are gettin' exciting.
And how about a waterwitch?
No, but I do have...
A Ragemaster?
That's NSA grade.
Serious hard-on when that showed up.
Yeah. I know what you mean.
Is all of this equipment illegal?
Well, with this kind of technology,
legality is a bit of a moving target.
- Ah.
- I figure justice is as justice does.
If the government
can use this shit to spy on us,
why shouldn't we be able to spy on them?
Missed you, buddy.
I married my husband
when I was 22 years old.
I felt like I was a very lucky woman.
Then he lost his job.
And he started drinking.
And then... beating me.
I could guess how bad the beating would be
by the hands of the clock.
Time was a source of terror.
But in here, every moment
spent free of that man is a gift.
But... why are you here?
Because I put rat poison in his bibimbap
and killed the motherfucker.
She did her husband, too.
He was a bad man.
And you?
I pushed my father's wheelchair
down an elevator shaft,
with him still in it.
In this country, sometimes the only place
you can find a brave and honest woman
is in prison.
You guys have been so good to me.
I just want to do something for you.
Hernando, I know you've been dying
to come to this restaurant
ever since Lito talked about the food.
I saw you and your little
emoticon sad face.
Hm?
But here you are... out in the world,
sitting next to each other.
Come on! Let's enjoy it.
This is not working, Daniela.
We went to the wrestling thing together.
- It's different.
- Why?
Because that was a guy thing,
and this is a romantic restaurant?
Exactly.
You worry too much.
This is totally working.
If a photographer comes up
or someone that wants an autograph,
all Hernando has to do
is stand up and glower at them,
and I guarantee everyone in this room
will believe he's your new bodyguard.
- I... I can glower. I... I can do that.
- See?
Hi. Um... can we take a picture?
I'm sorry, Mr. Rodriguez is busy.
- It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
- Oh... Oh, OK.
Thank you. Hi.
- OK.
- Thank you very much.
- We have to go.
- This is my fault.
- It was my fault.
- It isn't your fault.
- Relax.
- Let's go, please.
The man is eating. Leave him in peace, OK?
Leave him in peace!
Oh, my God!
- How was it?
- So good!
I... I believed it.
I mean, I fully believed it.
I believed it, too.
Oh, my God.
Clouds!
Look at them! So close.
Beautiful.
How amazing is this, huh?
I've never been on a plane.
Hey, you are so lucky.
No, I'm not lucky.
Of course you are.
You are flying, above clouds.
Privileged, not lucky.
You are lucky 'cause you are
still able to see your father.
That is something I dream about,
but will never happen again.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I lost my father,
but I still have my mother.
I wish I could see the world that simply.
Riley, look out of the window.
Those are actual clouds.
But what if something terrible happens
because of me going back?
What if something wonderful happens? Eh?
First class, huh? It's nice.
I love you.
Mr. Gonzalez! How are you doing?
My new bodyguard, Hernando.
My girlfriend, Daniela.
You'll be seeing a lot of them.
Hi, Pop.
- I missed you so much.
- I missed you, too.
Thank you.
OK, OK, you have to admit
that was the best night out of your lives.
This, this was our first night out ever.
Ever.
- Champagne. Orange juice.
- Welcome home!
- Make you a drink?
- What the fuck are you doing here?
"The fuck"?
The fuck is the reason that I'm here.
Lito, call the police.
Hey!
I know I'm the bad guy,
that's why I wore this mask.
But this is not the real me.
Shh.
See?
I'm not the bad guy.
I'm the sad guy.
- You're drunk.
- You're gonna have to leave, Joaquin.
Enter the hero. The big hero.
The man every guy wants to be
and every girl wants to fuck.
Don't touch him.
Oh. Who's the tough guy? Huh?
He's my bodyguard, Joaquin. So, please.
He just broke a photographer's arm.
There's been enough violence for tonight.
That's cool. Cool, cool.
No violence.
I don't want no violence.
What do you want, Joaquin?
I wanna know what I did wrong
and what he did right, that's all.
For starters... Lito's never hit me.
Wait, that's not fair.
This is Mexico. I am a man.
I was raised that way.
You hit your woman
to make her respect you. Fuck!
Well, Lito's twice the man you'll ever be!
I know.
Oh, fuck. I know.
That's why I'm here.
Why?
Because I want to see it for myself.
Wanna be a better footballer,
watch the best.
Wanna be a better baller...
do the same.
What?
I wanna see you fuck her, Lito.
Jesus Christ!
I know how it sounds, but please!
Give the guy a break.
You're the better man. You won.
You fucked her away from me.
So I just thought maybe I could
learn how to fuck her back,
or at least how to fuck the next her
away from someone else.
- That's it. I'm calling the police.
- Oh, no, no. Please. No, wait! Hey!
Listen to me. Wait, Dani. Listen to me.
Leave it! Leave it!
Get the fuck out of here!
- That's it.
- I don't want to go.
I'm leaving, I'm leaving.
Please. OK, I'm going. I'm going.
Lito, fuck her in good health!
My bodyguard.
I'm feeling very
Whitney Houston right now.
Amanita never told me
she was dating Robin Hood.
Nom's got this whole secret identity, Mom.
Silicon Valley nerd by day,
political hacktivist by night.
- She tried to go straight...
- Hey, I would never go straight.
She tried to play by the rules,
and they tried to lobotomize her.
I'm sensing a bit of a negative vibe here.
You guys picking up on this?
Your Spidey sense tingling
or something, 5-0?
Maybe this wasn't
the most prudent decision.
- We'll be all right.
- Y'all just need to be cool
and let me do the talkin', a'ight?
You know, I still can't believe
how you're just taking this all in stride.
If someone told me they were hearing
other people's voices in their heads,
I'd be sure they slipped off
their medication.
Child of the '60s.
If you didn't hear voices at least once,
you were doing something wrong.
You sure you got the right kid?
- I never seen him with your crew.
- That's the point. He's an eye.
You're not supposed to see him,
but he sees you.
Like the man says,
when you look into the ghetto...
the ghetto looks back at you.
There was a time when people
who heard voices were considered saints.
It wasn't a sign of madness,
it was a sign of the miraculous.
Still is, as far as I'm concerned.
Oh, yeah!
- Game time! You niggas are sweet!
- Yeah!
Yeah!
Oh, shit.
Ludicrous Lincoln. Fuck me.
Why'd it have to be Lincoln?
You and Lincoln got history or somethin'?
My boy got all Romeo
with the former Ms. Ludicrous.
Damn, Will!
When Nita was very young,
I took her to her first July 4th picnic,
and she got scared by the fireworks.
Still hate 'em.
Why celebrate with symbols of war?
- Wars are always a failure.
- Yes, honey.
But she got frightened,
and before I knew it, she was gone.
Lost. A million people around me.
I felt this panic starting to rise up,
but before it hit,
I suddenly could hear her.
Not her voice.
It was the sound that she used to make
when she slept against my chest.
- Aw.
- It was a... a feeling, or a vibration,
and I... I followed it straight to her.
Waffle cone stand.
I'm a simple girl.
No one believed me when I told them
how I found her, but it didn't matter.
I knew what had happened.
I'm one of those people
who's comfortable with the idea
that there's more going on in this world
that we don't understand
than all the things that we do.
Hey, you know I'm askin' myself,
can this be that Officer Gorski?
The very same Officer Gorski
that tried to stick his pork
- into my motherfuckin' pussy?
- OK...
- Shut the fuck up, Officer Gorski!
- Back the fuck up.
Uh-uh. Nah, man. Ludicrous,
you gave me your word that you...
Word don't mean shit to this punk.
Let's all remember that
he has somethin' you want,
you got somethin' he want.
C'mon, man.
You know the fundamental
nature of the universe
is not competition, Officer Gorski.
No? What is it then?
Commerce.
Find anything new on Metzger?
Checking his travel records,
he has been all over the world.
London, Istanbul, Switzerland,
Seoul, and Iceland.
- Hm.
- And these are his insurance records,
basically his work history
over the past year.
You're looking for the operation
he was gonna do to you.
Exactly. He's performed it three times
in the Bay area.
What happened to the patients?
Two of them died.
And the third?
What is it you want?
- Diplomatic immunity.
- What?
We want you to leave us the fuck alone.
That includes your motherfuckin' pork.
Fuck this shit.
How about we haul you in right now
- for obstructing a federal investigation?
- Nobody's arresting anybody.
If the information is good...
- Can I help you?
- I'm here to see Niles Bolger.
- He's a patient here.
- And you are?
I'm his niece.
4K, show him.
All right.
- You saw the van pull up?
- I knew somethin' was up.
Smelled like the Feds.
- They pull anything out of the building?
- Check it.
Who's in the bag?
Still unidentified at this point.
- You get the license plates?
- Of course I got the plates.
What you think we are,
amateur hour and shit?
I'll start a trace.
Oh, yeah. Scary dude.
The way he talked and everybody jumped,
figured he was the big dog.
Hey, you know this dude, 5-0?
The procedure was performed
by Dr. Metzger, right?
Yes, Dr. Metzger
personally handled Mr. Bolger.
Uncle Niles, it's me, Nomi.
No... Thank you.
Nom!
Wha...?
That could be me.
It's not. You're here.
Just promise me that no matter
what you have to do,
you will not let that happen to me.
Promise?
I promise.
I'm just saying that if our equipment
was used in some sort of criminal act,
- clearly, we're not responsible.
- Clearly.
- We'll need to know who rented this.
- Paperwork's in the back office,
but without some sort of
warrant or something...
The warrant's gonna go to your bosses.
Probably have to file with corporate, too?
Just to be thorough.
- Yeah.
- Trust me, man, you do not want that.
I'll make a copy. Here it is.
Can you open it, please?
They brought it back real clean.
Most thorough clean-up job I've ever seen.
- Not a spot on it.
- I'll bet.
Hey, whoa. Hey, hey, hey!
You OK?
No, I'm good.
From the day I decided to marry Rajan,
you have been sending me... visions.
You sent me a vision of a woman
taking her own life.
Visions of other people in distant places,
even in prison,
which could perhaps be a metaphor
for my situation,
intended for education and instruction.
But then, you sent me a vision of a man...
with a large...
trunk?
A very large trunk.
I am a little more than confused.
But... I trust you, Ganesha.
So I know there must be some meaning
to all of this that I cannot see.
And I wish to see. I wish to understand.
So help me, Ganesha.
Help me see what it is I must do.
Gods don't give a shit about us.
I speak from experience.
- Why won't you just leave me alone?
- I tried.
Believe me, I try not to think of you,
but every time,
it brings me straight to you.
At least...
you're wearing clothes.
It's nice here.
The weather's shit in Berlin.
It rains like this in Bombay...
but it's not so cold there.
So tell me... does he ever help?
- What?
- Your god.
- Oh. Of course.
- How?
I asked him to stop my wedding,
and he did.
You think he stopped your wedding?
Do you have a better explanation?
So you think our connection...
is a kind of miracle?
If I were trying to describe
this feeling...
the sensation of experiencing
the warmth of the sun,
the smell of jasmine and marigold...
while at the same time being soaked
by a downpour at an outdoor café...
the taste of strong coffee
still in my mouth...
I would say that the word "miracle"
sounds particularly appropriate.
Wouldn't you?
You slept well?
Best sleep I had in a long time.
- I made pancakes.
- Yeah?
That boy is one of them.
He's from Jaluo, the same as his father.
His father is dead.
Wh... Where do you want us to go?
Where can we go?
Send him back then.
But he's my son.
He belongs with his own people.
It is best for everyone.
- Shiro! Please don't do this.
- Let her go.
God damn you.
God damn your tribes and your bad blood!
You can all go to hell.
During your time of stay, you will
complete female vocational training.
Can you sew, Prisoner 773?
- No.
- Did your mother neglect you?
- My mother died.
- Oh.
You are very lucky, 773.
Here, you'll receive training.
Who will be her teacher?
Volunteer?
Or I will assign one.
Pardon, ma'am.
I will be her teacher.
773, move to this table.
- You know the rules.
- Yes, thank you.
You didn't have to help me.
I know.
Smells so good, Papa.
- You're not having one?
- No, I ate hours ago.
I wanted you to wake up smelling them,
but you must have been really tired.
I've been watching you on the Internet.
- You've had a lot of shows. Doing well.
- Mm.
Oh, it's nothing, just playing records
for drunk people trying to get laid.
Playing Beethoven's the same, you know.
The people are mostly too old and tired
to bother with the getting laid part.
You make music, Riley,
and for a moment,
people forget the troubles in their lives.
It's no small thing.
I'm very proud of you.
Thanks, Papa.
I have to get to rehearsal.
If you need to go out, Sven is next door,
and he can drive you anywhere.
I thought he would be out on his boat.
He heard you were coming,
dropped everything.
I told Sven I don't care
if anybody shows up tomorrow,
as long as my daughter's there.
I'll see you, honey. Bye-bye.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- Bye, Papa.
You should not have come back.
I was always afraid as a child.
I couldn't sleep if the light was off
or if it was too quiet.
I don't like the quiet.
I used to fall asleep
in my father's restaurant.
I've always hated being alone.
It's one of the reasons
why I love the festival.
Mommy!
Papa!
Come! This way! Come!
- Do you like this? Come on, here!
- Yes!
Do you want to see what he sees?
What who sees?
Ganesha.
Come, come.
Look there!
It made me a believer.
But you're a scientist.
I am.
My love for science
doesn't preclude my faith.
For me, science is another language we use
to talk about the same miracles
that faith talks about.
But... one language makes sense,
one doesn't.
Sense? What, like quantum physics?
Like a particle
that can be here and not here?
Or sense like gravity?
A force that no one knows why exists.
Only that if it didn't exist...
if there wasn't this
mysterious attraction...
this pull between objects...
then none of this would exist either.
Thank God for gravity.
Exactly.
Hey, Wolfie. Where the fuck are you?
What?
- I heard from Abraham.
- And?
He'll take the rest of the diamonds.
When?
I don't know,
but we're going to be fucking rich!
- Hey! This is great fucking news!
- It is.
So why do you look like
someone took a piss in your beer?
I've been thinking I want to
get out of Berlin for a little while.
- Oh.
- I need to take a trip.
Where?
India.
No, go around to the other side,
or the thread will break again.
Ssst! She's coming.
See you outside, bitch.
Or not.
Does this happen often?
Only when the sun is out.
Don't get into any trouble, Diana Prince.
Mr. Kabaka wants to see you.
Dad's here?
Dad, you came to pick me up!
How could I leave you alone
on your birthday?
I know you're just pretending to forget.
Happy birthday. You could have told me.
You know I like my secrets.
She is like her father.
And now, I have a little surprise for you.
Come with us.
♪ And I ♪
♪ Eee-I ♪
♪ Will always ♪
♪ Love Hernando ♪
- 'Morning, Whitney.
- Good morning.
- What time's call?
- Ten minutes.
Oh, so you're already late.
- Would you like to be a lot late?
- Why?
Why?
Who calls?
This is what our relationship has come to?
Texting me from inside of the house?
I didn't text you.
Fuck.
- Oh, Jesus.
- What?
Tell me this is a joke.
Oh, my God.
The son of a bitch
must have stole my phone.
- You took pictures of us?
- You took pictures of us having sex?
This could destroy my career,
my whole life.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
He could blackmail me.
- He's gonna blackmail me.
- No, no. No, no. I...
- We'll figure this out.
- No, I'm gonna talk to him.
I'll get the phone,
the pictures, everything.
It's my fault, and I'm gonna fix it.
I'm... I'm gonna fix it.
Fuck!
You sure Metzger's gonna be here?
Reimbursement receipts show
he comes in for a coffee
every day around this time.
We are creatures of habit.
Enter the creature.
Large non-fat latte.
Right on time.
What does that thing do again?
It uses its own network to clone the phone
that he's using with this one.
What if he doesn't check his e-mail?
Ever not checked your e-mail
while waiting for a coffee?
Ooh!
I'm in. Downloading contacts,
e-mails, calls, passwords.
Mm. You are kinda like
Robin Hood, aren't you?
What's he doing?
What?
He looked scared.
Makes you wonder who was
on the other end of that call.
Contact list shows "Dr. Matheson."
I know what you're thinking.
I know that look.
Don't. Don't do it, Robin.
Don't, don't, don't...
I thought we were clear.
Who is this?
Is this Nomi?
What?
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
What? Who was it?
I don't know, but he knew me.
Shit.
Metzger's booked
on the last flight to Chicago.
OK, what does that mean?
- He's not gonna be in his house tonight.
- You're crazy, you know that?
I have to get into his home network.
If these people know who I am,
then we need to start
figuring out who they are.
W-W-N-Double-D.
What would Nancy Drew do?
I sense a costume opportunity.
They're all yours.
She likes you.
She has a big heart.
I would do anything for her.
It's the same with you
and your mother, yes?
Come with me.
This love... my enemies
would call a weakness,
something to be exploited.
I disagree.
I mean, these men,
what do they hold in their hearts, huh?
Desire... lust... greed.
But I ask... are these men willing to go
as far as you and I for what they believe?
This one...
This one I was grooming
to be my number one runner.
Do you know what he did?
He watered down the drugs I gave him
so he could double-up on the money.
My reputation is only as good
as the products I sell.
Mr. Kabaka, I...
Am I willing
to let my business perish,
to let the life I've made for my daughter
be destroyed by greed and stupidity?
He understood the risk he was taking.
Wow, it worked!
You read that in a book?
The power of literature.
Amazing. Do you know what else
I read in a Lee Child book?
That you can use the crowbar as an alarm.
So if anyone pushes the door,
we'll hear it.
We make such a good team.
Maybe Bug's right and we should become
a crime-fighting dynamic duo.
I think we already are.
Wow.
- Zombie-making sure does pay well.
- Yeah.
This is really weird.
There's almost nothing personal.
This guy's about as interesting
as a mouthful of sawdust.
He doesn't even have
any porn stashed away.
No porn? He is weird.
Oh, my God! Nom!
BFF's with Cheney.
He's gotta be evil.
Uh-oh.
He can't be all bad.
OK, just a couple more minutes,
and I'll have the entire
hard drive copied.
Come, come, come.
What's wrong?
Hey.
- What happened?
- I don't know what happened.
Nothing happened.
It's the nothing that has me worried.
You went to see Abraham?
I did. Or at least I tried to.
- We had a date.
- He didn't show?
No. So I called. Nothing.
Went by his shop. Closed up. Gone.
Fuck!
I'm thinking about your passage to India.
Maybe you need a Sherpa or something?
- Hello?
- We're closed!
Please, please, can you help me?
Oh, what would all the damsels do
if I left the city, huh?
Oh, my God, Nom!
Hello?
Shit! It's Metzger.
I'm calling the police.
It's not done. It's not done yet.
You better get out of here
before they arrive.
Nomi.
Hi, Dr. Metzger.
Whatever brought you here,
I'm happy to see that you had a...
moment of sufficient clarity
to seek me out to get the treatment
that you... need.
It shows there's still time to help you.
I can have an ambulance here
in five minutes.
I'm not the one that's
gonna need an ambulance.
Go ahead, doc, make my day.
You must be Amanita.
What I am, doc, is your worst nightmare,
unless you put that phone down.
You both are in a lot of trouble.
Yeah, well you're about to get
an eyeful of Mace
if you don't start answering my questions.
We visited your little zombie prison
in Nightingale's.
Yes... I know.
I'm guessing that's the reason
my trip was canceled.
Who canceled it?
Was it Dr. Matheson?
How do you know that name?
She jacked your phone.
I called him. We had a little chat.
- Oh, no.
- Who is he, doc?
What have you done?
Nomi.
- Jonas?
- You've gotta get out of here.
- Why?
- He's coming.
- Is that Jonas Maliki?
- Who?
- Whispers.
- Who is Whispers?
- Oh, my God, you've killed us all.
He's here.
Niles?
Nomi!
- Come on! Nom!
- Wait, wait, wait!
Please, come on! Leave it!
- Help! Somebody help! Somebody!
- Help!
Somebody help!
Please!
Help us! Help us, please!
Hey doc, what's going on?
Please! No. No! No!
No! No!
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net