Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
(man) Why do you keep
looking out the window, Will?
You like the snow?
You know, for some people,
snow brings on a very specific feeling.
Uh, some love it.
It feels clean and pure, like a...
fresh start or a beginning.
For others, it's frightening.
Cold and silent and... isolating.
What are you thinking about
when you look at the snow?
That I'm gonna have to shovel it.
(soft chuckle)
Will, I'm gonna talk to you...
like I would talk to an adult,
because I think
you're a very intelligent young man
and you are capable
of understanding what I'm saying.
In group dynamics, there's something
psychologists call "savior behavior."
Often one person in the group feels...
like they need to save the others
from a threat or an emotion
that he or she believes is dangerous.
Sometimes those people... are children
of parents with drug and alcohol problems.
These people have had to...
save themselves
from the emotional consequences
of their parents' addiction.
Your father was unable
to find Sara Patrell
and you wanted to help him, didn't you?
And that's a perfectly
normal response, Will.
You wanted to help,
that's a good thing.
But sometimes when we try to help
one person, another person gets hurt.
Sometimes that person's ourselves,
sometimes it's someone else.
And I know your intentions...
weren't to hurt anyone,
but when you say you can see Sara...
or her ghost and talk to her,
it causes people a lot of pain.
Especially Sara's parents,
who are dealing with the worst thing
a parent can go through.
Now, I've been as honest
as I can with you, Will.
Can you do the same for me?
Are you still seeing Sara?
Shh.
No.
- (intercom dings)
- (woman) Welcome to Iceland.
Please remain seated with your seat belts
fastened until we reach the gate,
and the captain has turned off
the fasten seat belt sign.
(Riley panting)
Oh... I'm so cold.
Mm.
- It's as high as it'll go.
- (exhales)
(Magnus) Here...
take my coat.
(gasps, exhales)
No, no, no, no, no, you need that.
I'm hot-blooded.
Don't worry.
I want to keep you both warm.
Here.
(gasps, cries out)
- Oh, it hurts! A lot.
- I know.
(sighs) They're coming faster. Oh...
Don't worry, sweetie, I'll get us there.
Just-- Just hang on.
(wind howling)
(groaning, inhales sharply)
(groans)
What were we thinking with that midwife?
It was a stupid mistake.
No, it's not her.
It's me. It's the hex.
- I'm hexed. (panting)
- I've told you, it's not the hex.
You're magic.
You're the most magical thing
- that has ever happened to me.
- (laughs)
I'll get us there, I promise.
(cries out)
(both gasp)
(Riley gasps)
(Riley cries out)
(Riley screams)
(wind howling)
(Magnus whispers) Riley.
Magnus.
Riley... come with me.
(gasps softly)
Magnus? (panting)
(moans)
(gasps, panting)
(groans)
Magnus...
Magnus.
(whimpers, sobs)
Magnus... no.
Magnus...
Oh, no.
(sniffling)
(screams)
(gasping)
(sighs, gasps)
(groaning)
(cries out)
(screams)
- (grunting)
- (fabric ripping)
(gasping, panting)
(screams)
(gasps, panting)
(baby whimpering)
(crying)
(sniffling)
Oh, my Lúna.
My Lúna.
(sniffling) Someone's coming for us.
It'll be OK.
(whispers) Someone's coming.
(sighs) Will.
(whispers) I'm coming for you.
I have bad news and worse news.
- Start with the bad.
- I found out where they're taking her.
A research facility
controlled by BPO up the coast.
- That's good.
- Not really.
It's very heavily secured,
but I'm working on a way in.
OK, give me the worse news.
A private plane
was just cleared for landing
with a single passenger on board,
Dr. Ellison.
- Whispers.
- It's gotta be him.
- I'm ahead of him.
- Not for long.
A helicopter is there
waiting to pick him up.
- I'm gonna need some transportation.
- Car's just confirmed.
It's there.
- Are you Will Gorski?
- Yes, I am.
Welcome to Iceland.
Please, sign here.
When did I get expensive taste?
When I got access
to Metzger's credit cards.
Ha!
Enjoy the stay.
The facility isn't on any map,
but I've loaded the coordinates
into the GPS.
It says that you can be there in 20.
- I'll be there in ten.
- (engine revs)
(breathes heavily)
(wind howling outside)
(gasps)
(groaning)
(sniffling)
(panting)
(grunting)
(cries out)
(panting)
(shrieks, gasps)
(grunts)
(groans)
(sings softly in Icelandic)
(sings in Icelandic,
voice quavering)
(stops singing)
(gasping)
(whispers) I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(whispers) I won't leave you.
(sniffling)
I promise I won't leave you.
My baby... where is she?
(Yrsa)
You would have done anything for her.
You would have
given your life for your baby.
(whispers) Yes.
This... is your last chance.
Take it.
Protect them.
(overlapping shouts)
Riley.
(panting)
(Yrsa, echoing) Protect them.
(Will) Riley...
please don't do it.
I'm coming for you.
Don't give up.
(gasping)
(groaning)
(exhales)
(Jonas) It might be the best thing
that could've happened.
Why?
She'll be unconscious
when Whispers arrives.
Where is he now?
He just climbed into the helicopter.
He knows you're here.
Do you have a plan for getting in?
I'm going with a nine-millimeter
tucked under my arm.
(Sergei) Buffie doesn't trust you.
He believes you know
what happened to Steiner.
I've been trying to call my son
since yesterday, but he doesn't respond.
Do you know where Steiner is?
I do.
Where?
You told me you didn't
want to choose between him or me.
Now you don't have to.
Where is my son?!
I'd give you details...
but you can ask him yourself very shortly.
What?
You fuck! (grunts)
Careful.
I heard the shots.
I know the way a bullet sounds
when it hits Kevlar.
The bodyguard's gun is gone.
You son of a bitch!
- (gunshots)
- Did you kill my son?
(gunfire continues)
(screaming)
Kill that fucking cunt!
(gunfire stops)
(screams)
(banging against door)
(clicking)
What is happening?
I guess I've come to say goodbye.
(rapid gunfire)
This was your plan?
How was I supposed to know
he'd be wearing a bulletproof vest?
Who wears a bulletproof vest in real life?
(banging against door)
What are you doing?
I'm not like Sun.
I do not know how to use my fists,
but... that doesn't mean
I don't know how to fight.
(bottles clattering)
(banging continues)
I am not ready to say goodbye.
Oh, fuck!
(groans)
(wood creaking)
(clicking)
(slams gun down)
Why, Wolfgang?
Why?
You're family.
We raised you.
What kind of man
betrays his own fucking family?
You said that you would have given
everything to know who killed my father.
I give you that gift.
(shouting)
(gasping)
(choking)
(groans)
(grunting)
- (Wolfgang grunts)
- (neck cracks)
Oh, God.
Why?
You know why.
You always knew.
And still, you did nothing.
Wolfgang, I'm-- I'm-- I'm--
I'm so sor-- sorry. I--
Please...
forgive me.
You said... your blood is in my blood.
So is his.
My father... was a monster.
And so are you.
And so am I.
(sighs)
That's why you have to marry Rajan.
(gun clatters)
- Damn it!
- (Nomi) Stop the car.
What?
- No, no, no. That's him.
- I know.
Whispers is going to get there first.
He's already told security to be
looking for you. You need a distraction.
Stop the car.
Engine's in the back.
Oil line's along the driver's side.
Pop the trunk.
Find the oil line.
Break it.
- It'll destroy the car.
- I know.
It was Amanita's idea.
It's why we picked this car.
Men cannot stand
to see a beautiful car in trouble.
It's some kind of primal instinct.
Look at you, you're hesitating.
- It's a really nice car.
- See?
(sighs)
(hissing)
(tires squealing)
(Will)
What am I supposed to use to get away?
You're the one that jumped on
the first plane to Iceland without a plan.
We're working on an exit strategy.
How about this guy?
He's on vacation.
In the meantime,
I think we found a way inside.
We've been combing through
the employee records, looking for a shell.
- I'm cooking the ID now.
- (Nomi) We'll send it when it's crispy.
You should be able to wave your phone
and just walk right in.
Seriously?
It's a square-cube law thing.
Bigger and more high tech a company is,
the easier it is to use the front door.
What about Riley?
I assume since none of us can reach her
that she's still unconscious,
which means that she's safe.
Safe? Here?
Could you explain the whole "don't look
him in the eye" bad guy thing again?
I--
I mean, 'cause I saw him.
I was afraid to look at him at first,
but... then I did.
Does that mean
he can see inside my mind now, too?
No, no, no. Jonas explained it.
- No, he's like us.
- He's sensate.
- He can only connect with other sensate.
- So she's safe.
Except for the fact that a man that uses
zombies to murder people knows who she is,
the police are looking for her,
she's using equipment
that could get her 20 years in prison,
all while aiding and abetting
her fugitive lover.
Is that what you mean by "safe"?
Hey, Nom, it's OK.
You love her a lot.
In my book...
safety's always been highly overrated.
- (sighs) Such a shame.
- It's a '14.
It's only a year old, man.
Oh, hey, man. You've gotta see it.
It's totally fucked up.
(man) Oh, my God!
- I still got nothing here.
- It's on its way.
- You sure this is gonna work?
- (Nomi) It'll work.
- Hey.
Your name is Fred Sloughman.
Fred Sloughman.
Consolidated Medical Waste.
Consolidated Medical Waste,
here to check out your... medical waste.
- You been cleared?
- Yeah, right here.
(rapid beeping)
- It's not working.
- Step over here.
- (Will) I don't understand.
- Um...
Step to the side.
It's not working.
- It should.
- Um...
- Turn up the brightness.
- Just a second.
Try it again?
(beeps)
- Sorry.
- Technology, huh?
(exhales)
Her blood pressure's dropping.
I can barely read her heartbeat.
Riley, open your eyes.
When I give instructions,
I expect them to be followed.
She went berserk. She grabbed a gun.
I had to use Rocuronium to put her down.
I want this woman conscious
as soon as possible.
She's no use to me in this condition.
If we're not careful,
she could go into anaphylactic shock.
You didn't expect this, did you?
Have you made a mistake?
Wake her up, now.
(Will) This place is huge.
- Know where she's being held?
- No.
- Why not?
- I'm not the Wizard of Oz.
I only have access to what's in their
computer system and she's not in here.
- How do I find her?
- (Lito) I'll find her.
Lito.
Don't worry.
- Do I know you?
- Yeah.
We had sex.
Wha-- Oh. Uh...
- (stammers) Eh... It-- That was--
- Very special.
Oh, hey... Uh...
We're on a clock here, fellas.
Follow me.
- How will you find her?
- It's a secret.
I'm very good at secrets.
(Lito) Oh, my God... what a day.
What a day.
(sighs)
- He can be difficult, can't he?
- (scoffs)
You mean Dr. Ellison?
- Yeah.
He told me that I should
pay attention to you because...
he says you are very good.
He has a lot of respect for you.
Really?
(chuckles)
I thought he was about to fire me.
- Welcome to my daily life.
- (chuckling)
I don't know how you could stand it.
Well... the work is important.
Yeah, of course.
Once in a while, I get to meet someone
who understands... how hard this job is.
- Mm. Yeah, yeah.
- You know?
And who happens to be very...
very attractive.
(laughing)
(sighs)
- I have to get back to work.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- What room was she in again?
- Um...
- Sixth floor, 620.
- Oh, yeah.
Clever, Mr. Gorski.
We don't know how he got clearance.
Ms. Marks, no doubt.
How's that exit strategy coming?
- We're going to need some help.
- Whose help?
Mine.
What can you do to help us
without him knowing?
In 12 minutes,
an ambulance is going to arrive,
because someone who works here
is on our side...
and is right now
pretending to have a heart attack.
Where is Mr. Gorski?
Sneaking away behind you.
Double the security
around Ms. Gunnarsdóttir.
- Sweep the facility.
- Done.
I don't like games.
That's a pity. I love them.
- She's definitely on this floor.
- Got it.
- The ambulance just arrived.
- Shit! Four guards.
Is that all?
Whispers knows where you are.
Give him a message.
If he thinks he can stop us,
he's going to need a lot more men.
This area is off-limits.
- (Sun grunts)
- (man screams)
- (man shouts)
- Aah!
- (all grunting)
- (man yells)
(shouts, gasps)
(Riley gasping)
(gasping)
Riley.
It's me.
(singing in Icelandic)
(whispers) Will...
Are you real?
Left. Go left.
I'm not gonna be able
to carry her out of here.
- We have to wake her up.
- How?
I don't know.
(Kala) I do.
(voice quavering) Set her down.
Sugammadex is the only
safe recovery agent for Rocuronium.
Combined with a little adrenaline...
This will be very violent,
but it'll wake her.
(gasping)
(whispers) Will.
- I'm here.
- (panting)
- You shouldn't have come.
- Why?
Because everyone around me dies.
- (electricity surging)
- (groaning)
- (whimpering)
- Now... Shh.
- How are they planning on leaving?
- (grunts)
Ah.
The ambulance.
Ambulance is parked in the garage.
Take the elevator.
No guns.
I want them alive.
(elevator beeps)
What is it? What's wrong?
Hello, Will.
Oh, no.
(elevator beeps)
Hey! No one can leave this building. Stop!
(grunts)
(man moans)
Shit.
Keys. Keys, keys, keys, keys.
There's no keys.
This is not a problem.
The Van Damn has been stolen many times...
and you learn many tricks...
in order to steal it back.
OK. Ah...
(engine starts)
Whoo!
Easy.
(helicopter blades whirring)
Will, this is foolish.
I see and hear
everything you see and hear.
Wherever you go, whatever you do,
whatever you think... I will be with you.
- Will... it's over. He's won.
- No.
You're afraid.
We're gonna get out of here.
There is absolutely nowhere to hide.
How are you supposed
to get away from a helicopter
when there's just one long road?
Oh, yeah, I got it. I got it!
- A weather map?
- Helicopters fly by sight.
They're not good in fog or rain.
The weather changes drastically
with altitude, to lose these guys,
- all they gotta do is head here.
- Oh, my God, I love you!
Will, up ahead there's a road to the left.
Take it.
(tires squealing)
Will?
Enough.
I know you.
You are a police officer.
You are sworn to protect people.
It's in your blood.
It's in your heart.
I know you won't kill us all.
You can't do it.
Maybe I can't...
but I know who can.
- (gasps)
- Pull up!
- Oh, no.
- What?
- We can't go this way.
- Why not?
Please, don't take me there,
not to those mountains.
- It's the only way.
- (gasping)
- Will, please go back.
- Why?
- Go back!
- We can't!
Please!
- (gasps, screams)
- (tires squealing)
(gasping) Oh, no.
- Oh, no, no, please don't take me back!
- Riley, what--
- (moaning)
- (Will) What is it? What's wrong?
(cries out)
(Riley yelling)
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
(Will gasping)
Oh, hurry up. (exhales sharply)
(groaning)
What? What's happening?
I don't know.
I can't reach either one of them.
They were there heading into the mountains
and... now they're gone.
(door opening)
(Will) Riley!
Riley!
(gasps)
- (panting) Riley... are you OK?
- (sings softly in Icelandic)
Stay with me.
I'm gonna get us out of here.
We're gonna be all right.
I wish that were true.
But we both know it's not.
Listen to me, Will.
You have very little time.
Whispers is getting into a car.
He'll find you shortly.
Once he has you, it won't be long
until he finds the rest of your cluster.
There's only one way.
(echoes) Protect them.
It's the only way.
(Will sobs)
It's OK, Will.
I was supposed to die here.
No. No.
No.
(gun thuds)
Riley...
Whispers saw me.
He's in my head.
As long as I'm unconscious,
he can't see what I see.
That's why I shot up with all those drugs.
In a minute,
I'm gonna be unconscious.
Our only chance is if you get
in that ambulance and drive us outta here.
Riley...
if you don't...
we're all gonna die.
(whispers) I can't.
I can't.
I can't leave her.
Riley, please.
I'm so sorry, Will. I can't do it.
(sobbing)
I know how much it hurts.
I know you want to lay down here
and never get up again.
I know it, 'cause I feel it.
(sobs) I can feel it.
And that means that somehow,
somewhere...
you can feel what I'm feeling, too.
I love you.
That's why you can't give up.
(whispers) I love you.
(softly) I love you.
(fading) I love you... I love you...
(sings softly in Icelandic)
(acoustic rock song plays)
Is he sick?
No, he's OK.
Everything's OK.
(exhales)
(whispers) You did it.
You saved us.
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net