Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
Do you know that feeling
when you're sitting in a movie theater
and everyone's laughing at something
- and you just don't get it?
- Yeah.
Like all the time.
This is where I'm at right now.
I'm sitting looking at the sunrise,
the city,
and I'm wondering, how can something
still look so beautiful
after we saw what we saw?
It just doesn't seem right.
No, it doesn't.
Are you all right, dear?
- I need to use the ladies' room.
- Go on.
Aah!
My God.
What happened to him?
It was... my fault.
I wanted to prove something.
I wanted to change something
that can't be changed.
What?
The past.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Dani?
Daniela?
- Where are you?
- I did it.
I got my phone back.
Everything's fine. I fixed it.
How do you know?
How do you know
everything's going to be fixed?
It just is, all right?
- Why are you whispering?
- Is she coming back?
I just wanted you to know
you don't have to worry.
- Are you coming back?
- I better go.
What did she say?
She said everything's going to be fine.
She fixed it.
She got the phone back.
Is she still with him?
- Huh?
- I don't know.
But this is good news, isn't it?
Hey. Hey, hey!
Is Jela home?
Fuck you!
You are looking very well, Elena.
Shithead, it's Motherfucker.
How do I tell them apart if you
keep calling all my friends motherfuckers?
Oh, it's this motherfucker.
Here.
It's the nicest thing a motherfucker's
done for me today.
To the ancestors.
You and Elena are not getting along?
You have money. What's wrong?
It's me. She hates me being home.
I can't blame her.
I'm a stallion, Capheus.
I go a little crazy locked up in a barn.
Maybe it's time to go back to work.
Are you serious?
I realized today I cannot
keep doing what I'm doing.
I've not yet told Mr. Kabaka this.
I'm not sure I know how
to tell Mr. Kabaka this.
But I cannot go back there again.
The matatu is our work, eh?
Real work. Clean work.
You saved my life once again,
my friend!
Light of my life,
I'm going back to work!
- Is that true?
- Ah.
Thank you, Van Damme!
Let's go inside.
- Yeah, sure.
- Come, come, come!
Ah... Oh, shit.
You'll never have outside privilege
if you continue teaching me.
I rarely get to go out.
But today looks beautiful.
It does.
They let us paint outside.
You like to paint?
I don't mind staying in.
Helping you makes time go quickly.
Soo-Jin!
Why does she choose you?
I'm fast.
I tried working more slowly once.
That...
That did not work out very well.
Bitch!
What are you doing?
That's not done.
Pick that up!
Get back to your seat!
My mother did not teach me to sew,
but my father taught me business.
This is called "second mover advantage."
The second mouse enjoys the cheese.
Today, you go outside. She sews.
Thank you.
You've known him a long time.
How did you meet?
Detention.
Welcome to my office, newbie.
Have a seat.
I'm Felix.
Wolfgang.
Wolfgang?
Nobody's named Wolfgang.
OK... Wolfie.
- What are you in for?
- Fighting.
Cool.
Where are you?
At the movies.
With my family.
Makes sense.
Why?
Felix loved the movies.
We cut school to watch films all the time.
No one will remember
if we were good men or bad.
All that matters is that
two stood against many.
This film's a masterpiece.
So grant me one request.
Grant me revenge!
And if you do not listen...
then to hell with you!
You finished!
I did.
Thank you for teaching me.
No, thank you.
This is our mural of happier times.
I'm painting my three sisters.
I miss them.
Do you miss your family?
No.
I miss my dog.
You're welcome to paint your dog.
Or anything else.
Sometimes... it feels good to remember.
I don't know why he liked me.
In those days, when we moved
from East to West Berlin,
I was the kid everyone hated.
Hey, you! Commie!
Your shitty country is ruining ours.
Get the hell out!
You don't belong here!
You better go.
- No!
- Go!
My dad says you're
costing us billions in taxes.
You're going to start
paying us back... now.
Come and get it!
Aah!
"No one will remember
if we are good men or bad!"
You're dead!
"Only that two stood against many."
That was your childhood?
No.
That was nothing... compared to my father.
Life is simple, boys.
Life is just five things:
eating, drinking, shitting, fucking...
and fighting for more.
I didn't say anything about crying.
Crying is for bitches.
That what you are?
A little bitch?
"Conan, what is best in life?"
He's crazy.
"To crush your enemies,
to see them driven before you!"
He would do anything for you.
He's my brother.
And not by something
as accidental as blood...
by something much stronger.
What?
By choice.
Is that your mother and you?
She took me to the Spring Festival.
We had ice cream.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
I know people like you.
You think you're better
than the rest of us.
Not better or worse, just different.
You got a smart mouth.
Only if one assumes that a master's
in economics constitutes a smart mouth,
as opposed to educated.
Many educated people are quite stupid,
and many stupid people
like to start fights for no good reason
on a truly beautiful day.
Let us not ruin it.
Only thing I want to ruin
is that smart mouth.
Stop fighting.
I don't want to hurt you.
Aah!
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh.
I was worried about you.
I'm OK.
You still in London?
I'm home.
This is where I grew up.
Let me show you.
This is the piano where
my dad practices every morning.
When I was little, I used to lay
on this rug with my coloring book,
listening to him.
When I think of the word "happy,"
that rug is the first thing
that comes into my head.
Your dad's kind of a big deal, huh?
Mm-hm.
Especially in Iceland.
Icelanders really like it if you get
famous somewhere else and then come back.
They respect you more that way.
Oh, is that your mom?
She's beautiful.
She was.
Oh, she passed away.
Mm-hm.
- Sorry.
- Are you talking to me, honey?
No, I was just talking to myself.
Here you go.
- Still black with one sugar?
- Thanks, Dad.
That's how I take my coffee, too.
- I've gotta go.
- OK.
You're home.
Oh, I can't believe it.
- See you tonight.
- See you later.
He seems like a nice man.
He is.
Why did you stay away so long?
Oh, you don't have to explain it.
I ask way too many questions.
Bad cop habit.
A lot of things that are
hard to talk about happened here.
We know what you did for Soo-Jin.
So, this is your home?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's kinda small, you know?
Cops don't get paid a lot.
I like it.
This is so cool.
Wow.
You should come to America sometime.
Chicago's got a great music scene.
Uh, jazz, blues, house... I could show you
around the city before you even got here.
I could show you around Reykjavik.
So cool.
I want to see the volcano
no one can pronounce the name of.
Eyjafjallajokull?
God bless you.
Oh, my God, what is that?
You sleep here?
You get used to it.
Oh, my God!
Wow!
The fuck you doing, Gorski?
Huh?
Everything is so much better now.
- Yes, so much better.
- Uh, we spoke to the astrologer,
and he says that the horoscope
for the new wedding date
is even better than the last one.
- The last one was not bad.
- No, no, not bad.
- But this is better.
- So much better.
Clearly, the gods wanted it this way.
So, uh, you wish
to use the temple of Ganesha?
Yes.
Since I was a child, I have always
felt a closeness to Ganesha,
that he sees through my eyes
and I see through his.
I can't remember the last time I smelled
your sukuma wiki and ugali.
Ah.
I'm feeling much better.
But you are far too thin.
It makes my heart sing
to see you cooking again.
You were never good
at hiding your emotions.
What is troubling you, my son?
This medicine...
the man I was getting it from...
I won't be able to get it
from him anymore.
Troubles like this seem far less troubling
on a full stomach.
Family is so important.
- What do you want?
- I had a family once.
- Get out!
- Capheus!
I had a sister.
We were tight, like you and moms here.
One day, me and Mr. Kabaka
had a disagreement.
I came home and she's lying there,
a wire around her throat,
her scalp torn off.
That's what Mr. Silas Kabaka taught me.
- Love ain't nothing but a black hole.
- No, no!
What do you want?
Come on, hero.
What does every person on this planet want
whose life has been fucked up
by another person?
What the fuck do you think we want?!
What does he want?
And why here?
Why did he want to meet here?
She said it was halfway.
She wanted to make it easy.
Oh, come on, Hernando. This is Joaquin.
He wanted us to meet in public.
- Maybe you should wait in the car.
- I think I should wait in the car.
Yes. Yes.
Hi.
Dani...
Thanks.
Sorry it's so late.
It's the only time he could do it.
It's not a problem.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine. I'm good.
He hit you.
We were... negotiating.
No, no. This is wrong.
You cannot go back to that asshole...
I told that asshole I would marry him
if he left you alone.
What?
Lito!
Hernando, no. No, no, no,
don't worry about me.
What? This is crazy. Come on!
What?
We make choices... and life
has a way of making us pay for them.
That's a line from
The Price of Life is Death.
And you were so great in it.
The world is inspired
by your movies, Lito,
and I want you to
continue making them, OK?
Dani...
Hernando, I'll be fine.
If life has taught me anything,
it's that... I can take a punch.
Goodbye.
Don't have too much fun without me.
- What am I going to do? I don't know.
- Yes, you do!
You cannot give them the child.
You know that!
If I don't, they will come back.
You've heard them.
That's what men do, they make threats.
And you, more than anyone, know they have
the ability to carry those threats out.
And you, more than anyone...
you know that their threats
and even their violence...
cannot touch the things that matter.
Mama... is it completely
crazy to realize...
even after gangsters
have threatened your life...
how lucky you are?
Not at all.
- Baby O'Riley!
- Ah! Sven!
It's been so long.
- Riley, it's good to see you.
- You, too.
How's the boat?
Uh, it creaks, it groans.
Not as fast as it used to be.
We have that in common.
Skoal.
It's so good to see you, Riley.
For weeks, all your father's talked about
is you coming home.
We're all happy to have you back.
It's so nice to be back.
This is your home, after all.
Born right there.
Ellen and I still laugh about that night.
Gunnar won't let me buy a new phone.
- He calls it the umbilicus.
- Does it even work anymore?
I have a cousin in the highlands.
We have the last two rotaries in Iceland.
- Is your dad coming over?
- No, he's practicing.
- Big day tomorrow.
- Mm.
Sven, you know I don't drive anymore.
Whenever, wherever,
just knock on my door.
Thank you.
Don't ask me how I know this,
but that woman right there is Nomi Marks.
She was scheduled for a brain operation,
she disappeared.
This is the federal BOLO for her.
And the guy she's talking to
is Niles Bolger.
He had the same brain operation
two years ago.
He's now living as a complete vegetable
at Nightingale's, until last night.
Do I even want to know
how you're accessing this shit?
I used my dad's old captain's clearance
for the requisition.
Oh, my God.
Yesterday, Bolger receives a package.
The FedEx guy doesn't
know what to do with it.
I know what you're gonna do.
You're gonna bury us with this.
Watch this.
Whoa.
Last night, a guy who couldn't drink
from a coffee cup without drooling
went on a shooting spree.
One of the people he killed
before eating his own gun
is the doctor who performed
the surgery on him,
and was scheduled to do
the exact same thing to Nomi Marks.
OK, if this was an episode of CSI,
I'm hooked,
but cut to the goddamn chase and tell me
what the fuck this has to do with us.
The company that paid Dr. Metzger
to perform those surgeries,
that paid for the long-term care
of Niles Bolger,
is the exact same company
that rented the white van
that made one of the most dangerous
terrorists in America disappear.
And this company is called?
BPO, the Biologic
Preservation Organization.
"A multi-national research group
studying the human genome
in the search for positive
and consequential mutations."
Well, that doesn't sound
sinister at all.
These guys are seriously funded.
I'm finding embeds to DARPA,
the World Science Foundation, the WHO...
How are you able to access
their financial records?
You're the guy that helped me
get out of the hospital.
- That's right.
- What guy?
He's standing right there
and he's a cop.
Chicago PD.
A lot of that stuff is illegal.
So is using your father's
clearance codes
to access federal security information.
How did you know about that?
Know what?
I'm not sure.
OK, you've having a conversation
with a cop in Chicago right now?
Yeah, I guess I am.
Cool.
FaceTime without a phone.
I mean, not exactly.
We can know things and feel things.
She can't hear you.
Who the fuck you talkin' to, man?
Noth... I'm just talking to myself.
You were at the shooting last night?
You've killed us all.
The only reason they would do something
like that is if they felt threatened.
That means we're getting close.
It also means that if they have
no problem killing their own people,
then they'll have no problem killing us.
Did you find anything
on Metzger's hard drive?
So you know about the hard drive,
but you don't know what's on it?
No one gave me a rule book here.
I'm just trying to go with it.
Uh... Basically, they've been
paying this guy a butt-load of money
to fly all over the world
and lobotomize people.
I think he hooked up
with the company when...
When he was a medical student
at the University of Chicago.
- Mom!
- That picture.
- Wait.
- Coming.
- I know that guy.
- How?
When Bolger put the gun in his mouth,
I saw a reflection in the mirror
that wasn't his.
It was that guy.
I'm Dr. Friedmann.
Senior Officer with the Biologic
Preservation Organization.
That voice...
I know that voice.
I thought Nomi
was still in the hospital.
I know you think
you're doing the right thing,
trying to protect someone you care about,
but this woman has a terrible disease...
- It's him!
- Who?
It's that guy.
He says that the guy
at the door is that guy!
So, for your safety, we are putting you
into protective custody.
- What?
- Don't look at him.
- Why?
- Jonas told me that's how he hunts.
I have a warrant to search these premises,
and if you interfere,
you will be arrested and prosecuted
- to the full extent of the law.
- You've gotta go right now.
- You can't do this.
- Oh, yes, we can.
No! What are you doing? No!
What are you... No, wait!
You can't do this!
Amanita! Amanita!
OK, out the window,
over the balcony.
- The alley will take you to Corbett.
- No.
- You have to come with me.
- No. You need time.
I'll stall them. Go!
Go, honey! Go!
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, my God. Neets.
Um... Um... OK.
Shit.
- Is that you, Mom?
- I'm a federal agent. Open the door.
A federal agent?
- Open the door, ma'am, now!
- Uh... I'm, uh...
kinda in the middle of something.
What the fuck?
I am changing my tampon,
you fucking pervert!
- Please come with me.
- Can I finish, or do you want this, too?
Huh? Huh?
You want it? You want it? Fucking take it!
- Get eyes on the back alley.
- Copy that.
- Stop! Don't move!
- Oh, God.
Hands in the air!
Oh, my God.
I don't want to go back to the hospital.
Cop guy, where are you?
- What are you looking for?
- It's the feds. They found her.
- How do you know?
- Gorski, the captain's office, now!
We've got her. Back of the hill.
Someone, please help me.
Stay calm.
Are you in my head or are you here?
I'm in Seoul. I was sleeping.
Ah, shit!
- Get on your knees!
- Oh...
- Who are you?
- I'm Sun.
We don't have time for this.
He's gonna call for backup.
Backup on Corbett.
This guy's right-handed.
He's gonna go for your right wrist.
Now!
Throw the gun.
Get on the bike.
Is there a problem, Captain?
Shut the door.
Stop her!
I don't know how to drive.
I do.
- Are you crazy? Oh!
- I saw this in Hard Target.
Jean-Claude attacked
when everyone thought he was going to run.
Whoo!
It worked better in the movie.
Look, Gorski, this isn't a movie
or a fucking TV show.
I gave you clear warning
that if you didn't follow orders,
- there would be consequences.
- OK, but, can I explain?
I can explain,
same way they explained it to me.
You're suspended without pay.
Captain.
Captain, you know that is not fair.
What the fuck you talkin' about, Gorski?
Not fair?
This is the real fuckin' world.
Nothin's fair.
Drop your badge, sign the paperwork,
get the fuck out.
It's El Caído.
You said he would come for you.
A man must never be judged
by the length of his gun,
or the size of his fortune.
In the end, we'll all be judged
by the courage of our hearts.
And cut!
Give me one more, please. The line!
Lito, you're beautiful.
- You sure?
- It's great, we're fine.
We have it, OK?
And your, uh... friend is here.
Oh, yeah. My bodyguard. Yeah.
- Hello, Kala.
- Papa-ji.
- I had no idea you came to the temple.
- I don't.
No, I came here to see you.
- Can I have a word with you?
- Yes, of course.
I was considering our conversation
about continuing the wedding as planned.
It's just that, uh,
the events of the past few days
have led me to... reconsider things.
- Reconsider?
- Yes.
You know, I don't believe in
gods and miracles.
Our fates are governed
by the choices that we make.
Others, of course, will argue that luck,
good or bad, is a factor, but I disagree.
Luck can only offer an opportunity.
But without the will
to make the right choice,
luck would be as meaningless as...
as that elephant-headed god.
To me, the idea of praying to a god
to somehow influence my own fate
is both primitive and terribly sad.
I'm sorry, I don't think this is the place
to have this conversation.
Something's wrong?
What is it? Is it Joaquin, right?
- He's gonna blackmail me.
- No.
No, no, I haven't heard from him.
Is it Daniela?
In a way.
I guess, in a way, she reminded me of
the things I had allowed myself to forget
because I feel so strongly about you.
Hernando, your tone is scaring me.
What are you talking about?
I love you, Lito.
I love you more than I have ever
loved anyone in my life.
I love you, too.
But I can't be with someone
who allows someone else to be hurt
in order to protect their career.
- I wish it didn't end this way.
- It doesn't end this way.
What are you talking about?
This isn't my fault.
Hernando, she did this to herself.
She admitted it.
You cannot leave me for that.
This is not fair.
- I know it's not fair.
- So what do you want me to do?
You want me to throw
my whole life down the toilet
- because of a woman I barely know?
- I don't know what you should do, Lito.
All I know is what I have to do.
Are you gonna break up with me
because of her?
- No, it's not her.
- Then what?
"In the end...
we will all be judged
by the courage of our hearts."
It's a stupid line from a stupid movie.
Hernando, please.
I'm sorry, Lito.
- Goodbye.
- No, please, no. Please don't leave me.
Hernando.
Hernando!
Hernando, please don't leave me, please.
Here we go. Let's shoot!
I was hoping that after
our conversation is over,
when you pray to your Ganesha,
he'll also tell you that what you are
going to do is the right thing to do.
- What I am going to do?
- Mm.
You are going to call up my son
and you are going to tell him
that you cannot marry him.
What?
You know in your heart
that's the right thing to do.
I could see it in your eyes.
That's why you stopped the wedding,
to keep yourself from
committing this terrible mistake.
- That's not true. That is not why I...
- Of course... Of course it is true.
- I...
- It was a mistake for both our parts.
I should have never given my blessing.
But now, luck has given us
another opportunity to correct it.
All we require is the will...
No!
Help!
Papa-ji!
Papa-ji?
Help! Help!
Somebody! Help!
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net