Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
(♪ The Weepies: "World Spins Madly On")
(no audible dialogue)
- I was just...
- ...thinking about you.
Cheers.
I'm Riley, by the way.
I'm Will.
You're a cop?
You're a musician?
No. Just a DJ.
That's-- That's cool.
- You live in Chicago?
- Yeah.
You're in, uh... London, right?
Ah, that's so cool.
I've always wanted to go.
Well, here you are.
Yeah, but...
I know.
Are we going crazy?
I got an idea.
Give me your phone.
All right, now, there's no way
you could know this number, right?
So when you hit this button...
that phone shouldn't ring, right?
OK. Call me.
(phone ringing)
Hey, Diego!
- Hey, Diego.
- What's up?
There's something going on with
my hearing. Can you pick this up for me?
Yeah.
- Hello?
- Uh, hi. Is Will there?
Yeah. Hang on.
- Some chick with a weird accent.
- Weird accent?
- She sounds hot.
- I like him.
- Thanks, man.
- All right.
- Safe to say we're not going crazy.
- (over phone) ...not going crazy.
- Oh, my God. This is so cool.
- (over phone) This is so cool.
Have you had any other visitors?
Jonas said that there were eight of us.
Jonas?
He was with the woman who shot herself.
Angelica.
How did you know that?
I'm not sure.
That... That time you came to the church,
you seemed really scared.
Like something happened.
You OK?
I-- I am sorry.
It's none of my business, I get it.
I have complicated friends.
Hey, tell me about it.
I should probably go to bed.
Yeah, well, must be
pretty late there, huh?
DJ hours.
(inaudible chatter)
They took it all, Neets.
My laptop, back-ups...
Oh, my God.
They even took all of my journals.
This isn't fair.
- None of this is fair.
- No, it's not.
- I didn't do anything.
- I know, sweetie.
This isn't gonna stop. They're never
gonna leave us alone, are they?
Unless we make them.
Uh-oh.
You got that look in your eye.
Fuck these guys, Neets.
We'll need a place.
Someone who can keep a secret,
someone we can trust.
Shit just got real.
- (clamoring)
- (reporters) Ms. Bak! Ms. Bak!
(overlapping chatter)
(reporter) How long ago
did you start embezzling?
Do you regret what you did?
For my actions taken...
to embezzle funds from this firm,
I have offered to surrender to police,
pending trial.
I acted alone in this.
Neither my father, my brother,
nor any other member of my family
were involved or profited in any way.
That's all I have to say.
(clamoring resumes)
How long ago did you start embezzling?
How could you spend that much...
(sniffing)
Riley.
Shugs?
(softly)
Why don't you take Bambie for a walk?
(sniffs)
(sighs) Sorry.
(door closes)
(softly) Riley, Riley, Riley, Riley...
Where is it?
The money.
I don't have it. I gave it away.
'Course you did.
Look at my face, Riley.
Look at my face.
Look what they did to me.
This is nothing compared
to what I will do to you.
The money and the drugs...
or you die right now.
I swear I don't have them.
I threw them away.
I was scared.
I didn't know what to do.
I'm so sorry, Riley.
I don't believe you.
No, no, no, no.
Please, Nyx. I promise you--
- (glass shatters)
- (gasps)
(screams) Please, someone help!
Somebody help me! Oh!
(gasps)
(gasps, panting)
I hate violence.
But sometimes, violence is necessary.
Violence changes things.
(sobs, gasps)
I love how violence
can change something
as simple and ubiquitous...
as a plastic bag here,
into one of the most terrifying objects
in the world.
(screams)
(gasps)
Riley...
Let's see if this experience...
has changed your answer.
Riley, Riley...
Where's my money?
(sobs) I don't know.
(whispers) No, please.
I don't know.
(sobbing) No!
(screams, gasps)
(gasps)
(no audio)
(grunts)
- (bones crack)
- (screams)
(groans)
(coughing, gasping)
(gasping)
(indistinct murmurs)
(panting)
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Mom.
I am so glad you called.
Baby.
(kisses)
(relieved sighs)
Hi?
We decided it might be wise
to keep a watch on you.
We all watched, all night,
but very quietly.
Huh.
Thank you, but I'm fine, I think.
You must understand,
when you went over like that so suddenly,
we were terrified
something has happened to you.
Nothing matters to us
more than your well-being.
Thank you, but I'm fine, really.
You're sure?
Yeah. Why?
Rajan is waiting here downstairs.
(moans)
(floorboards creaking)
Hello, again.
Oh, no.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have already ruined my life.
I didn't ruin anything.
You didn't want to marry that guy.
That is not for you to say.
Maybe not, but you wanted me to say it.
You don't know what I want.
Don't I?
No.
OK, I don't know what is going on here,
if-- if I am totally losing my mind,
or if one of the gods or goddesses
is angry with me and has sent a demon.
A dangerous pervert demon
who never seems to have any clothes on.
- Germans are not so uptight about nudity.
- Mm.
This is not about nudity, OK?
This is-- This is about decency.
It is about privacy.
If you were so concerned with privacy
and decency, why did you look?
I did not.
Yes, you did.
You looked then and you're looking now.
(sighs) I'm not.
Listen...
I don't know what's
happening to us either,
but I do know that from the moment
I first saw you, I wanted you.
And somehow, I feel
that you want me, too.
Oh, my God.
You are a demon.
- (heavy metal music playing)
- (crowd cheering)
(whistles)
This is-- This is the Manichaean drama.
It's life and death, good and evil.
(crowd cheering)
La parca negra is a symbol.
He is the devil in our lives.
For some, he can represent the government,
the class system
or any form of oppression.
But for most of us,
he is that fear we're afraid to face.
Come on!
You will discover that Hernando
thinks a lot about everything.
- That's what I love about him.
- I get it.
(crowd clamoring)
- You love this, don't you?
- Mm!
- I love art, all kinds of art.
- (laughs)
I mean, this is a dance
that is also a fight.
The struggle that takes place in the ring
is a reflection of the struggle
that takes place in our minds
and in our hearts.
At some point,
we all encounter our own parca negra.
He is that thing we are afraid of,
that thing that stops us from becoming
what we know we can become.
Until we defeat him,
we will never know peace.
Oh!
- Get him!
- Come on!
- (shouts in Spanish)
(crowd clamoring)
(crowd noise fades)
Mm.
Your father's patra ni machhi
is a gift to my mouth.
Every taste bud
is dancing and singing his praise.
It's his grandmother's recipe.
Mm.
Amazing. Absolutely amazing to me
how lives can span generations
in something as simple as a recipe,
or something as complex as DNA.
By all accounts, great-grandmother
was a very difficult person,
who told my father he was a terrible cook,
and hated the way he made
the patra ni machhi.
Well, back then,
it must have been very hard
for a woman with her obvious talents.
Even today, she would have a hard time
getting the same recognition
your father gets just because he's a man.
Well, our parents do
the best that they can,
and it's our job to forgive them.
Rajan, you're not making this easy,
but I think we should just get on with it.
- Get on with what?
- I know why you came here.
I know that if it was you that had fainted
just before you were to marry me,
oh, dear, I'd be absolutely sure
that you hated me
and that you didn't
want anything to do with me.
- Kala, slow down.
- So I completely understand
if you came here because
you don't want to marry me any longer.
And you don't have to worry
about protecting my feelings--
Kala, please, just listen.
For me, what happened at the banquet
was a part of the story.
I'm here because I'm hoping
that it's not the end of our story.
For me, I love what happened.
I love it because it makes
our wedding something special.
Everyone else looks at pictures
of their wedding
and the story is always the same.
They have nothing to say.
But I imagine telling our children
how their beautiful mother
took one look at their father
and fainted straight away.
It is a great twist.
You can see why we have to
get married now, can't you?
(Silas) Van Damme.
I hear your mother continues to improve.
Yes. The medicine is helping.
Thank you.
There's no "thank you" necessary.
I'm not in the business of charity.
You're thinking,
"What will he have me deliver this time?
Drugs? Weapons? More coconuts?"
(chuckles)
- Amondi. How are you?
- I'm good.
I'd like you to meet someone.
- This is Capheus.
- Hi.
Hello.
Wow! What have you made, my dear?
- It's a home of the Little Mermaid.
- I love it.
This is the sort of place I wish I lived.
Me, too.
Why don't you get your camera,
so you can take a picture of it
and ask how much it'll cost to build?
- Really?
- It never hurts to ask.
My daughter, Amondi,
does not see me as someone to fear.
She sees me only as Papa.
(sighs)
She has leukemia.
To combat this, she receives
induction therapy, stem cell therapy,
at the World Health Organization Center
on the Nakuru Road. You know it?
My cars are known to my enemies.
The road to Nakuru is long.
No one would think to look for her
in that pile of shit you call a bus.
She's the most important thing
in the world to me, Capheus.
Everything I do
is to build a life for her.
Every breath I take,
I breathe for her.
Without her, my life has no meaning.
And if something happens to her...
neither will yours.
Prosecution submits the defendant
has violated 356 and 231
of the Korean penal code.
We also confirm the interrogation record,
signed by the defendant.
(man) Your Honor, my client
has signed the confession,
but wishes to pursue a jury trial
for purpose of latitude in sentencing.
In order to properly prepare our case,
we ask for the right to post bail.
- Does the prosecution object?
- Yes, we do, Your Honor.
Of the 30 billion won
the defendant stole from investors,
most remains unaccounted for.
It would be easy for someone with
Ms. Bak's connections to flee the country.
My client has a clean record,
and has willingly cooperated--
Only after the investigation began,
Your Honor,
when exposure became inevitable.
I concur. Bail is denied.
(gavel slams)
(crowd murmurs)
All I'm saying is... guys are talking.
What guys?
Just guys.
If someone's got a problem with me,
I should know.
It'll just piss you off.
All right. You know what?
I don't give a shit anyway.
That's your problem.
I saw Sobczak's eyes
after your exorcist act,
and if I were you,
I'd start giving a shit.
And what about you?
You think I'm crazy?
Oh, yeah. But I like 'em crazy.
(laughs)
(overlapping chatter)
- (speaking Swahili)
- (overlapping chatter)
Wham-bam, there comes our man.
We are locked and loaded, partner!
Look at the Rat Van. (laughs)
Sinking ship. (mocking laugh)
(Capheus) Sorry, Jela.
- The Van Damn is taken today.
- What?
- Get these people off the bus.
- Are you crazy?
It is also taken for tomorrow
and the day after,
- chartered for private use.
- By who?
Silas Kabaka.
He paid a week in advance.
Here.
- You mustn't do this.
- I have to.
He can get medicine for my mother.
Real medicine I cannot afford.
Take the money, please.
(sighs)
Remove all clothing.
The shower is there.
You have two minutes.
You're shy.
There are no doors.
You gave up your right to privacy
the minute you arrived here.
We are on the location of
Even Angels Must Earn Their Wings
with its star, Lito Rodriquez.
So, Lito, can we get a little
up close and personal here?
Sexual history.
- Any STDs?
- No.
- Cold sores? Crabs? Lice?
Have you ever been checked for HIV?
Excuse me?
What about family?
What about them?
- Family is very important to me.
- Answer the question.
When was your last intercourse?
Some time ago.
Well, Lito, we don't have a lot of time,
so I'll have to be direct.
Stand up,
and remove your underwear.
And squat over... this mirror.
Hey, whoa, no, no, no. Hey.
I'm not doing that.
You're not doing what?
Oh, my God, Christina.
There is a line,
there's a line in the script,
and I think that was--
(laughs)
That was just an actor's reflex.
- Oh! (laughs)
- I'm sorry, I-- Can we do that again?
- Would you mind? Are you still rolling?
- Yes, please!
Keep rolling, guys. Keep rolling. OK.
Um... Let's just cut to the chase.
You've been involved
in some of the steamiest scenes
we've ever seen on television.
What is the secret to be a great lover?
I've never thought about it.
But, I guess...
First, you have to be selfless.
The pleasure of your lover
must become your own.
But at the same time,
you must also remain... selfish,
because wanting someone so much
that it feels the same as the need...
to eat...
or to breathe...
this is where desire
becomes love, I guess.
(exhales)
Did you get that? OK. Yeah, yeah.
- 'Morning, Van Damme.
- 'Morning, Amondi.
You can call me Diana Prince.
Ah! Wonder Woman.
Shh! They call it a secret identity
for a reason.
OK, OK, got it.
(clears throat)
(Neets moans)
- 'Morning.
- Good morning.
(Neets) Mm...
My baby's back to feeling herself again.
Mm... I don't know if it's the fact
that I still have my brain,
- or that you saved my life...
- Mm...
(♪ Fatboy Slim Featuring Macy Gray:
"Demons")
...or...
the fact that...
I'm laying here in your bedroom,
thinking about you sneaking out
as a teenager.
Mm-mm. Out of that very window.
(laughing)
To go make out with--
What was her name?
- Zuzu.
(laughing)
- Zuzu. Mm.
- Mm.
(Diego) That's what I'm talking about.
You get into your own head too much,
Gorski.
(grunts)
That's what happened at Slugger's.
Hello, ladies. Lookin' good! Strong.
Come on, push it.
Five more, five more.
- (grunts)
- Seven.
Look at that.
You feel how it burns? Yeah?
(groans)
It's mind and body, yo.
Gotta tend to the temple.
Keep it flowing.
(grunts)
Push it out. Push that out!
(exhales)
- (laughs)
- Aah!
I gotta be honest with you, Will.
When I first got assigned to you...
that fucking name, "Gorski"...
I was picturing
some typical Chicago boover,
with a big-ass mustache
and gut dripping over his Bat belt.
But I gotta say,
you keep that shit looking tight, man.
- Ooh!
- Tango and Cash, baby.
(song continues)
(inaudible chatter)
I am gonna make love to you.
Like the first time we kissed.
(song continues)
(moans)
(gasps)
(groaning)
Aah!
I just had one of the best
orgasms of my life.
(laughs)
It's my turn.
(Jean-Claude grunting)
- (clears throat)
- (Nomi) The question is,
why these people, why these minds?
Why not a mind that feels, I don't know,
more in sync with my own?
- Maybe that's the point.
- How so?
I teach a class on evolution
every semester,
and we talk about the engine of evolution,
which is variation.
I imagine that to be something more than
what evolution would define as "yourself,"
you'd need something different
from yourself.
(creaking)
(guard) You'll sleep here tonight.
Tomorrow, you'll be transferred
to Cheongju Prison.
It's completely crazy-making
how all of these emotions,
they just come bubbling up out of nowhere.
Sounds like menopause.
Emotions are connected to the nervous
system, which would be affected by
- what is happening to your brain.
- Yeah. 'Cause what I want to know,
is there a way that I can stop it
from happening, or at least control it?
Like ADD, where I can take a drug
and limit the effect that it has on me?
Or is it like Alzheimer's,
and that sense of me-ness will slowly,
inevitably disintegrate?
(crying)
(softly sobs)
Hello?
God, I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I thought I was alone.
Me, too.
I'm Riley.
Sun.
Sun?
Seriously?
- Yes.
- Wow, that is so weird.
Why?
Look.
(Sun) "I have conversed
with the spiritual sun."
I come here after working a long night,
to smoke, and... converse with the sun.
I would kill for a cigarette. (sighs)
- All I got is hash.
- What is hash?
It's like pot, but better.
Will this work?
Can't hurt to try.
I can taste it...
but it's more like a... memory.
It makes you feel good?
Sometimes.
In Iceland, we have a saying that
it's not the drugs
that make a drug addict,
it's the need to escape reality.
I understand.
Why are you here?
If you don't mind me asking.
(sighs)
I'm afraid I've just made
the biggest mistake of my life.
(man on screen) Ah!
- (man yells on screen)
- Time to go?
Good, let's go.
Watching Van Damme again?
Ah, yes.
Jean-Claude is a source of inspiration.
Inspiration to do what?
To believe you can make a difference,
that if you are brave,
you can fight to make the world
a more equal and just place.
Hm. I like Jean-Claude.
He wants to do the same thing
my dad wants to do.
- Really?
- Yes.
My dad says there are a lot of bad people
trying to hurt us and take our home away.
So we have to be brave and fight,
just like Jean-Claude.
So we are both in trouble
because of someone else's crime.
I knew Jacks was no good.
I knew what Joong-Ki was doing.
Why are we here?
Have you heard of the Hidden People?
In Iceland, there are small people,
like elves, who live in the land.
When I was young, I went into a cave
and I heard one singing.
She was singing a song my mother
used to sing to me when I was young.
It's quite a terrible song
about a mother having to kill her baby,
but I always found it so comforting.
I heard her voice
several times over the years.
She told me I was born with a hex,
and that if I stayed in Iceland,
bad things would happen to me,
and to the people that I loved.
And then my mother died, and...
And I believed it was my fault.
My mother died when I was young, too.
I had no voice telling me
that I was hexed,
but I still believed
somehow it was my fault.
Oh, I want to go home. (sighs)
I want to see my father.
You should go.
I'm afraid.
Don't be.
Right now, you're safer there
than where you are.
Tomorrow, I go to prison.
Are you afraid?
Don't be.
Why?
Because you're safer there
than where you were.
Mm... Mm!
What was that for?
I don't know.
Just felt like something
I needed to do.
I like that.
My child.
So beautiful and strong.
I'll always love you.
Remember to be careful, child.
They are afraid of you,
and they will hurt you if they find out.
Find out?
What you are.
What am I?
(whispers) The future.
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net